Guide to the Women's Center records, 1970-2005, bulk 1983-2005 UA.09.17.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- A2001-42, 1983-1999, bulk 1989-1999, 3 boxes
  - GPWN Mentoring 1996
    - Mentoring Evaluations, 1996 (Box 5)
    - GPWN Mentoring Information Packet, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Mentoring Files, 3 MS Word 2.0 files and 1 MS Excel file; approximately 0.4 megabytes. (Box 5)
      Digital files consist of letters of assignment to mentors and mentees, as well as a database export of mentors and mentees.
  - VOICES, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - VOICES, Spring 1999 (Box 5)
  - General Programming, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Senior Women Seminar Series, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Senior Support Group, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Co-sponsored Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Grad Resources [resources/issues concerning female graduate students] (Box 6)
  - Women in Science and Engineering (WISE) Programming 1994-1998, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Lady Blue, 1994-1998 [a capella group] [photographs] (Box 6)
  - Out of the Blue, 1996-1997 [a capella group] (Box 6)
  - Cleland, 1996 [all female selective living group] (Box 6)
  - Academic Deans/SASS, 1994 [Sexual Harassment Protocol] (Box 6)
  - Summer Protocol, 1994-1995 [Sexual Assault Support Services] (Box 6)
  - Planning, 1970-1994 (Box 6)
  - Students as Leaders (Committee and Conference, materials and readings), October 14, 1997 (Box 6)
  - "Practicing What We Preach," Diversity discussion, June 3, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Campus Community Development (CCD)
    - Planning, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Staff Notes 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Staff Notes 1996-1997 (Box 6)
    - Evangelical Groups Workshop, September 1996 (Box 6)
    - Diversity "Team," 1997 [traveling diversity dialogues meeting] (Box 6)
    - Staff Notes, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Randall Kennedy, October 1997 ["Conversations on Race: Policing and Race Relations"] (Box 6)
    - Robert Reich, November 17, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Peter Applebome, February 6, 1998 ["Building Community: conversations on Race, the Media, and Campus] (Box 6)
  - Mary Lou Williams Workshop/Conference, April 18, 1998 [Visibility/Invisibility: African-American Students at Duke] (Box 6)
  - Women's Center Press, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Women's Center Space/Few Federation Renovations and Repairs, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
  - Safety Task Force, 1994-1996 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, July 1995-June 1996 (Box 6)
  - Staff, 1994-1995 -- Administration (Box 6)
  - Women's Center, Phone Statistics, 1991-1995 (Box 6)
  - Student Staff Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Women of Color, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Duke Student Government, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Femilist, 1994-1995 [Duke Mailing List] (Box 6)
  - Synergy Proposal, Student Affairs, April 1995 (Box 6)
  - East Campus (Duke Magazine Article), December 1995 (Box 6)
  - Residential Options Discussion, (Housing and Plans), 1994 (Box 6)
  - Visiting Committee, November 13, 1994 [for Student Affairs] (Box 6)
  - Janet Smith Dickerson, 1994-1995 [Vice-President of Student Affairs] (Box 6)
  - Meetings with Maureen/Family, 1993-1994 [Maureen Cullins-Dean of Campus Community Development] (Box 6)
  - Maureen [Cullins - Dean of Campus Community Development], 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Alcohol at Duke University, 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Alcohol, 1994-1996 (Box 7)
  - North Carolina Governor's Institute on Alcohol and Substance Abuse - Duke Report, April 1995 (Box 7)
  - Campus Climate, 1993-1996, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Staff Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Staff Meeting Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Staff Meeting Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - Resource File, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Survey-Women's Center/Women's Studies, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Women's Center Quickie Brochure, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Chronicle/Dialogue Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - North Carolina Women's Legislative Agenda, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - "Men and Gender Issues" -- David Guttesman, 1990 (Box 7)
  - ACPA Article (MAC) "Gender Issues Programming for Men" (Box 7)
  - Duke Gay and Lesbian Alliance -- Aurora [Newsletter], 1989 (Box 7)
  - AIDS Quilt Bus, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - "Women at Duke…A Room of Their Own" -- Tobacco Road, February 1988 (Box 7)
  - Duke Housestaff Spouse Connection, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Duke Women's Coalition-A History and Analysis, 1987-1997 (Box 7)
  - Sexual Harassment
    - Sexual Harassment Research Project, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
    - Sexual Harassment Task Force Policy Drafts, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Sexual Harassment Duke Policy and Procedures, 1987; 1992 [clippings] (Box 7)
    - Sexual Harassment - Duke History, background information, 1989-1992 [includes policies re: sexual harassment; romantic relationships: faculty student dating; discriminatory harassment] (Box 7)
    - Sexual Harassment Task Force, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Beckum Group, 1991-1992 [Leonard Beckum University Vice President and Vice Provost] (Box 7)
  - VOICES
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7)
    - Spring 1994 (Box 7)
    - Working Documents, Fall 1994 (Box 7)
    - Staff Reports, Spring 1995 (Box 7)
    - Fall 1995 (Box 7)
    - August 1996 (Box 7)
    - Spring 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Staff Reports, 1992-1994, 3 folders
    - Staff Report, Zeba Ali, undated (Box 7)
  - Running Club, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Movie Series, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Adrienne Rich, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Graduate Women of Color, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - "In the Spirit: A Celebration of the Challenges and Courage of Women of Color," 1992- 1993 [Women of Color (WOC) speaker series] (Box 7)
  - Women of Color, 1993-1994 [Tiffany Speaks] (Box 7)
  - Women of Color Retreat, January 1995 (Box 7)
  - Women of Color, 1994-1995 [Stacey Ebron] (Box 7)
  - Women of Color Planning, Summer 1995 (Box 7)
  - Speaker Series, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate Decisions Panels, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Current Propaganda [Women's Center Flyers], 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Publicity Opportunities, Triangle, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Calendar, Fall 1996 [includes a calendar from 1994] (Box 7)
  - Girlstown [Film], 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Calendar, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Co-sponsored Events, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Issues Lunches, 1993 [Laura Rosenstein, work study programming coordinator for the Women's Center] (Box 7)
  - General programming, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Oleanna: A Power Play by David Mamet, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Practical Workshop Series, Spring 1995, 1994-1995 [contains the monthly staff reports for the series] (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Programming Ideas, 1993; 1995; undated (Box 7)
  - Rape Awareness week, March 29, 1993 - April 1, 1993 (Box 7)
- A2002-68, 1993-2000
  Accession contains material concerning the program BASES (Building Awareness through Shared Experiences), a program seeking to ensure the welfare of all first-year women. Accession contains digital BASES files including member lists, BASES Board information, flyers, memoranda, and the BASES Constitution. Inclusive dates for the accession are 1993-2000.
  - BASES (Building Awareness through Shared Experiences) (Box 7)
    - Forming BASES (Box 7)
    - BASES, 1996-1998 (Box 7)
    - Flyers (Box 7)
    - Chronicle articles (Box 7)
    - BASES, 1999 (Box 7)
    - BASES, 2000- (Box 7)
    - BASES digital files, 329 digital files in MS Word, Adobe Pagemaker, MS Excel, WordPerfect, and unidentified file formats; approximately 5.7 megabytes.
- A2003-37/ A2005-0077, 1992-2001, 2 boxes
  Accession contains subject files mainly concerning events and programming materials. Groups/programs present include GPWN, VOICES, Women's Center Art Gallery, and BASES. Accession A2005-0077 was filed with A2003-37 and can be found in box 9. Inclusive dates 1992-2001.
  - Women of Color, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Tuesd'8, 1996 [a series designed to give students a break from studying and to provide them with a chance to socialize with fellow residents] (Box 8)
  - Planning/Staff Meetings, Summer 1996 (Box 8)
  - Campus Community Leadership Institute, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Campus Community Development (CCD) Staff Meeting notes, 1998-2000 (Box 8)
  - Alcohol/Drug Initiative Task Force, 2000 (Box 8)
  - WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) Programming, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - UNC WISE paper, undated (Box 8)
  - WISE proposal, 1995 (Box 8)
  - WISE Task Force, 1998-2000 (Box 8)
  - GPWN History, 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - GPWN, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - GPWN, 1999-2000 (Box 8)
  - VOICES, 1995 (Box 8)
  - VOICES, funding sources, 1993-1998 (Box 8)
  - VOICES, Reference and history, 1989-1995 (Box 8)
  - VOICES, feedback, 1993-1997 (Box 8)
  - General Programming Program Evaluations, Fall 1995 (Box 8)
  - General Programming Program Evaluations, 1996 (Box 8)
  - General Programming 1997-1998 (Box 8)
  - General Programming Program Evaluations, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
  - General Programming, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - General Programming Program Evaluations, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - General Programming, Fall 1999 (Box 8)
  - Division of Student Affairs' Strategic Planning Committee
    - Student Affairs Staff Survey, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Student Affairs Staff Survey, Summer 1995 (Box 8)
    - Student Affairs Staff Survey, Spring 1996 (Box 8)
    - Student Affairs Staff Survey, Summer 1997 (Box 8)
    - SPC Committee Meetings, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Professional Programmers Group, meeting minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 8)
  - Art Gallery (Box 9)
    - General Art Gallery Information, 1993-1995 (Box 9)
    - Art Gallery Year End Report, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Art Gallery: Samples of Exhibit postcards, brochures, and flyers, 1993-2001, bulk 1994 (Box 9)
    - Art of Women art duke: Inaugural Exhibit, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Art Gallery Exhibit: Susan B.A. Somers-Willett, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Art Gallery: World Works International Student Art (Box 9)
    - Martha Hamblin's Show, 1993
      - "Visions of Femininity: A Photographic Exploration of Nudity" (Box 9)
    - Kim Fisher's Show, 1994
      - "Lesbian Identities: A Photodocumentary Exploring Lesbian Lives by…" (Box 9)
    - Chrissie Anderson's Show, 1994
      - "Sisters" (Box 9)
    - Eliza Day's Show, 1994
      - "Primal Colours" (Box 9)
    - Diana Rosenblum 's Show, 1994
      - "The Naked Truth about Women" (Box 9)
    - Portraits and Statements, 1994-1995 (Black History Month Exhibit) (Box 9)
    - Love Makes a Family: Living in Lesbian and Gay Families, 1994-1996 (Box 9)
    - "Warnings" Poster Exhibit, 1998 and "Wake up little Susie: Pregnancy and power before Roe v. Wade" (Box 9)
    - A Positive Life: Portraits of Women Living with HIV, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Galia Goodman, 2001
      - "Remember the Ladies words of courage, compassion, and challenge from women of many cultures" (Box 9)
  - Women's Center Staff Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - Women's Center Staff Meeting Notes, July 1998 to May 2001 (Box 9)
  - VOICES - Fall 1999, Special Edition, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - VOICES Printers, 1996-2000 (Box 9)
  - "Just Economics" workshop, 1998, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Religion and Feminism/Ethics, 1998 ["The Education as Transformation Project: Religious Pluralism, Spirituality, and Higher Education" Wellesley College September 27-28, 1998], 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Interfaith Dialogue, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Education as Transformation, 1998 [Wellesley College] (Box 9)
  - BASES (Building Awareness through Shared Experiences)
    - BASES, 1993-2002, 8 folders (Box 9)
    - BASES mentors, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - BASES Mentor Evaluations, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - BASES, Student Programmer's files, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - Students against Sweatshops, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Women's Action Research Project (WARP), Interim Report, 1992 (Box 9)
- UA2006-0047, 1984-2002, 4 boxes
  Major subjects/programs present include DARE (Duke Acquaintance Rape Education), Task Force on a Duke University Women's Center, Men Acting for Change, campus climate, sexual harassment, Women of Color, and Student Affairs.
  - Acquaintance Rape Presentation Flyer, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Duke Acquaintance Rape Education (DARE)
    - DARE Booklet, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Correspondence, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Correspondence w/ Univ. of Colorado, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Handbook (original), 1990 (Box 10)
    - DARE History, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Manual, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Manual Supplements, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Meetings/Notes, 1991, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - DARE Presentation Notes, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Programming/Roleplays, 1994 (Box 10)
    - DARE Programming, 1993 (Box 10)
    - DARE Resource Guide, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Staff/Schedule, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Training Manual (Bound), 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Training Sessions, 1991 (Box 10)
    - DARE Training Test, 1990 (Box 10)
    - DARE Training Test, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Training/Meeting, 1992 (Box 10)
    - DARE Videocassette, 1990 (T-120 VHS) (Box 10)
    - DARE Videocassette, 1991 (T-120SX VHS) (Box 10)
    - DARE Videocassette "Socialization: Chris South", 1988 (T-120 VHS) (Box 10)
  - Date and Acquaintance Rape Programming, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Date Rape and Sexual Assault Task Force, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Date Rape and Sororities/Greeks, 1989-1991 (Box 10)
  - Date Rape can be prevented - What you can do, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence regarding Date Rape on Trial, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Date Rape on Trial Discussion Guide, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Information Flyer on Date Rape on Trial, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Date Rape on Trial - Preparation for video, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Spring 1992 Version of Date Rape on Trial (goes with videotape) 1992 [5 ½" floppy disk] (Box 10)
  - Date Rape on Trial w/ stage instructions, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Legal Consequences of Rape Program, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Rape Articles ("A Rally Against Rape" and "Sexual Exploitation"), 1984 (Box 10)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault Bibliography, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Rape Awareness Week Flyers, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Rape Awareness Week Publicity/Media, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault Resource Flyer, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault Packet for Academic Advisors, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Rape Awareness Week - Flyer, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Rape Colloquium and Education, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Rape Crisis of Durham, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Rape Prevention for Gilbert and Addoms Dorm, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Rape Prevention - Medical Center, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Six-Week Educational Campaign on Acquaintance Rape, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Committee on Date Rape at Duke, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Unofficial Sorority Rape Survey, Spring 1990 (Box 10)
  - "I Tied a Ribbon Because…", 1991 (Box 11)
  - "I Tied a Ribbon Because…", 1993 (Box 11)
  - "Sounds Dangerous" Forms, Labels, 1992 (Box 11)
  - "Sounds Dangerous" (Orientation Program), 1990 (Box 11)
  - "Sounds Dangerous" (Orientation Play), 1990-1993, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - "Sounds Dangerous" Sales, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Alpha Tau Omega Program, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Annual National Student Conference, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Basketball Game Sponsorship, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Center for Teaching and Learning, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Discussion - "Responding to Rape at Duke," 1991 (Box 11)
  - "Feeling Good about Sex" Decision Making Program, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Gotcha! Campaign
    - Copyrighted materials, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Plan, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Requests, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Press, 1991 (Box 11)
  - GPWN Calendar, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Major Speaker - Dr. Williams "Contemporary Social Problems," 1992 (Box 11)
  - Major Speakers - Nancy Ziegenmeyer, 1991 [The Aftermath of Rape: Legal Alternatives] (Box 11)
  - Offstage Production "But I Said No," 1996 (Box 11)
  - Play "Disciplining Women," 1994 (Box 11)
  - Pledge Education, 1994-1995, 1997, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Professional Programmers Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
  - Program Sign-Up Sheets, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Programming Areas, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Programming Resources, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Project Build Crew Leader Training, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Project Build Presentation, 1991 (Box 11)
  - R.A. Training, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Safer Sex Week, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Talent Identification Program, 1994 (Box 11)
  - WISE Calendar, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Calendars, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Program Volunteer History, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Director's Report, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Advisory Board Meeting Minutes, September/October 1990 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Advisory Board Retreat Minutes, December 1990 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Programming/Budget Planning, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Director's Report, January/February 1991 (Box 11)
  - Director's Report, March, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Advisory Board Meeting Minutes, February 1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center, General Information, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Job Descriptions (DARE), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Goals and Objectives, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Orientation Guide, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center and SASS Annual/Semester Reports, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Programming Semester Report, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Women's Center Staff, Contact Information, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Student Staff, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Budget Narrative, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - "Men and Rape" Panel, 1990 (Box 11)
  - "Men Against Rape" Handbook, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Men on Rape Flyer, 1991 (Box 11)
  - MAC, MADR, DARE meeting, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Men's Initiative, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Men Acting for Change (MAC)
    - MAC: "What's so sexy about pornography?" [contains slides and visual material for presentation] (Box 11)
    - MAC, 1993, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Brochure, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Program and Pledge Information, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Workshop Training Materials, 1991=-1992, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Men's Project for Campus Equality, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Men's Project Funding Request, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Men's Project Report, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Duke Men's Project, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Duke Rape and Sexual Assault Task Force
    - Agendas/Notes, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Minutes/Memos, 1990 (Box 11)
  - 684-SAFE Guide, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Crime Prevention and Safety Guide, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Crime Victims Handbook - Revised Crisis Center Handbook, 1985-1990 (Box 12)
  - Duke Safety Assessment, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Graduate and Professional Students Safety Guides, 1992, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - K. Wooden - Safety Proposal, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Monthly Report of Activities and Safety Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Public Safety Program, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Flyers, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven - Flyers/Ads, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Job Descriptions, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Materials, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Materials, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Resource Guide, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Training, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Training Evaluations, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Training Manual, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Training Manual (bound), 1993 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Training Manual and Protocol Guide, 1993, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven - Program Services, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Safe Haven Volunteers, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - Reception for Public Safety, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Safety Orientation, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Safety Phone Number Distribution, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Safety Presentation, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Safety Task Force, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Security Task Force Correspondence, 1993 (Box 12)
  - "Sexual Assault" Undergraduate Judicial Code, 1989-1991 (Box 12)
  - A Handbook for Survivors of Sexual Assault, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Duke Hospital ER - Sexual Assault, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Duke Sexual Assault and Intervention Handbook Draft, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Duke Sexual Assault and Intervention Handbook, Victim to Survivor, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Griffith Letter to Students re: Sexual Assault Judicial Changes, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Hamm-Alvarez Sexual Harassment Research Report, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Research Sexual Assault Coordinator, 1991, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Sex Survey, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Sex Assault and Relationship Violence on the College Campus Conference, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Personal Notes, 1995 (Box 13)
  - "Dealing with Harassment Concerns," 1987 [Mary P. Rowe] (Box 13)
  - Women's Duke Experiences Comparison Survey Report, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Newspaper Articles (various), 1988 (Box 13)
  - Women's Studies, Friends Newsletter, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Bates, Lisa "Is She Hot?" 1989 (Box 13)
  - Lisak/Roth/Luttrell, "Rape at Duke" 1989 (Box 13)
  - OPTIONS: A Dramatic Presentation of True Life Stories, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Paper: "The Socialization of Rape as a Cultural Norm…" 1989 (Box 13)
  - Articles on Rape at Duke, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Today Show, Interview, 1990 [Campus Violence] (Box 13)
  - Judicial Board - "Should I File a Complaint?" 1992 (Box 13)
  - Citation Verification for book on Campus Rape, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Duke News Service, 1993 (Box 13)
  - On Campus With Women - Keohane is President, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Article: "Women Leaders @ Duke: A New Generation," 1994 (Box 13)
  - New York Times: "With money threatened, colleges are moving on all lobbying" feat. Keohane, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Videocassette (VHS) - Fox 22 News, 1996 - Interview w/ Selden Holt and Amy Ellison on filming of and casting call for Kiss the Girls. (Box 13)
  - .edu the ratings, 1997 [U.S. News and World Report rating of colleges and universities] (Box 13)
  - Open Forum: "Apathy Plagues Feminism at Duke" and "Rape on College Campuses" 1997 (Box 13)
  - Duke University News - Memorandum (March), 1998 (Box 13)
  - Academics and Motherhood Articles, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Advisory Board Bylaws/Goals, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Advisory Board Correspondence, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Advisory Board Minutes/Memorandums, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Advisory Board Nomination Letters, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Abshire-Simmons, Martha - Profile, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Saleh, May - Letter to Maureen Cullen, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Time Availability Form, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Union Facilities Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Letter to Writing Course Instructors, 1990 [re: Rape Awareness] (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Faculty Education, 1991 [re: Sexual Assault] (Box 13)
  - Few Fed Space [for Women's Center] Letter, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Religious Life Personal Letter, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Smith-Dickerson, Janet - Director's Correspondence, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Academic Deans Correspondence, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Convocation, 1995 [President Keohane's convocation address] (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Keohane-Alumni, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Malhotra-Keohane, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Smith Dickerson-Keohane, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Higgins-Keohane, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Plummer-Keohane, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Keohane-Duke-Parents, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - Plummer-Keohane Memorandum, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Referrals, 2002 [community agencies] (Box 13)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services (CAPS), 1991 (Box 13)
  - CAPS/Women's Center Correspondence, 1991 (Box 13)
  - CAPS Colloquium on Sexual Assault and Harassment, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Relationship Violence House Course, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Gender Studies 247A, relationships and Sexuality, Final Exam, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Women as Leaders Course, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Flyers, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Get Involved Flyers (various), 1992 (Box 13)
  - Women of Color Celebration Week - flyer, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Senior Women's Seminar Series - flyers, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Student Health Flyers - PISCES and PICAD, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Student Health Information, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Service of Healing Program, 1991 (Box 13)
  - "Victim to Survivor" Booklet, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Harassments - Notes/memos, 1994, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Leave of Absence Policy, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Duke's Harassment Policy Pamphlet, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Domestic Violence Packet, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Law Enforcement Protocol, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
  - LGBT Materials, 1994, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - LGBT Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 13)
  - LGBT Correspondence, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Incest Resources Information, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Committee on Nondiscrimination Report, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Domestic Partnership Proposal, 1994 (Box 13)